<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>PyCon Israel 2024 - announcements</title><link href="https://shaib.github.io/pycon-il-2024/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://shaib.github.io/pycon-il-2024/feeds/announcements.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://shaib.github.io/pycon-il-2024/</id><updated>2024-07-25T12:30:00+03:00</updated><subtitle>PyCon Israel is a conference dedicated to the Python programming language, related technologies, and their use.</subtitle><entry><title>PyCon Israel 2024 Tickets Now Available!</title><link href="https://shaib.github.io/pycon-il-2024/tickets-available.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-25T12:30:00+03:00</published><updated>2024-07-25T12:30:00+03:00</updated><author><name>PyCon Israel Team</name></author><id>tag:shaib.github.io,2024-07-25:/pycon-il-2024/tickets-available.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;PyCon Israel 2024 tickets are available to buy&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We're happy to announce that ticket sales are now open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But first a few important points to note:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pricing Policy&lt;/strong&gt; - We have always strived to keep PyCon Israel
ticket prices low, to make the conference accessible to a wide and
diverse audience. In past years, ticket price was far below the
conference costs per attendee (PyCon Israel is run by volunteers, and
was never intended to make a profit). But as the majority of
tickets ended up being purchased by companies for their employees, it
meant that the conference was subsidizing these companies (with
volunteer work and sponsors money).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trying to come up with a pricing policy that makes more sense, this
year, we’re trying a different way. Tickets purchased by companies
will be sold at a price that reflects actual costs to the conference
(full price - 450₪), and tickets for individuals, at a more affordable
price (250₪). We trust conference goers not abuse this policy, and
hope to be able to keep the lower price available for individuals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workshop Tickets&lt;/strong&gt; - Same as previous years, there are separate
conference tickets (for the first day - September 16th at Cinema
City), and Workshop tickets (for the 2nd day - at the Microsoft
Reactor); Workshop tickets need to be purchased individually for each
workshop. Each workshop costs 20 ILS, serving as a 'commitment
ticket'. These tickets are not valid for the conference talks day, and
vice versa. We will refund the cost of the commitment ticket if you
attend the workshop. There are limited seats to each workshop, and
while we recognize the will to secure your spot, we also ask that you
not hold a ticket if you don’t really intend to come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, go &lt;a href="https://ti.to/hamakor/pycon2024"&gt;grab your tickets&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;(edited 25/7/2024 18:00)&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="announcements"></category></entry><entry><title>PyCon Israel 2024 Agenda Published</title><link href="https://shaib.github.io/pycon-il-2024/agenda-published.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-21T22:45:00+03:00</published><updated>2024-07-21T22:45:00+03:00</updated><author><name>PyCon Israel Team</name></author><id>tag:shaib.github.io,2024-07-21:/pycon-il-2024/agenda-published.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The PyCon Israel 2024 agenda is out&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;PyCon Israel is proud to present the agenda for the 2024 conference.
This agenda is the result of long hours of work -- by the submitters
of proposals which were chosen, and proposals which weren't;
by &lt;a href="https://shaib.github.io/pycon-il-2024/meet-pyconil-reviewers.html"&gt;reviewers&lt;/a&gt;,
and by the conference team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The agenda includes an opening panel, 27 talks and five workshops. We
believe it reflects our commitments to excellent content and to the
local community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go &lt;a href="https://shaib.github.io/pycon-il-2024/pages/schedule.html"&gt;check it out&lt;/a&gt;! We expect
tickets to be available later this week.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="announcements"></category></entry></feed>